#### Contact

Mandaue City, Philippines 09209294639 (Mobile) ronald.reyes.me@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ronald-reyes-014a22268 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Self-Directed Learning Goal Oriented Teamwork

### Certifications

Servicenow Course Certificate of Completion

Certificate of Completion - DICT MACH Python Courses

Mechanical Engineer

Certificate of Completion - MongoDB Essential Courses

### Honors-Awards

2022 Member of the CIT-U King's Court

**DOST-SEI Scholar** 

College Scholar Awardee

# Ronald Reyes

Appl. Systems Developer | Full Stack Developer | Mechanical Engineer

Cebu, Central Visayas, Philippines

## Summary

With my 2 years of work experience, I have established and maintained application systems that help business streamline their processes. My role is a junior software developer in a startup company, DIS Tech, specializing in full-stack web development and automation tools. Two sample projects that I led are Project Cortex Platform, which is initially a passion project and eventually adapted as the main tool replacing a legacy application and then Quote Module (Pricing App). I also became flexible in programming and IT related roles, which I get to experience hardware support, software maintenance, security (SSL) and server, database, and microsoft O365 administration.

One important milestone in my career is shifting from engineering related field to being a programmer, and this became my edge, having trained to be a critical thinker. I am very passionate to learn new things, especially in the advent of AI and Machine learning.

## Experience

DIS Tech | a Technoprobe company 1 year 1 month

Application Systems Developer September 2024 - Present (9 months)

Lapu-Lapu, Central Visayas, Philippines

Interface Solution Engineer
May 2024 - September 2024 (5 months)
Lapu-Lapu, Central Visayas, Philippines

Teradyne Interface Solution Engineer September 2023 - May 2024 (9 months) Lapu-Lapu, Central Visayas, Philippines

## Education

Cebu Institute of Technology

Bachelor of Science in Mechanical Engineering with Mechatronics, Mechanical Engineering · (June 2018 - July 2022)